{
    "id": "9d9cbf4f36a94fba97369dbd052bbaca",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I …………………………… the bags on the table.",
            "description": "To lay is to put something down. Laid is the past tense of lay. ",
            "answers": [
                "lied",
                "laid",
                "lay"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I earn …………………………. money than a sweeper.",
            "description": "We use less with uncountable nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "less",
                "fewer",
                "lesser"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………………………… to ride a bicycle.",
            "description": "Know cannot be followed directly by an infinitive.",
            "answers": [
                "know",
                "know how",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Every country has ………………………………. traditions.",
            "description": "It's means it is or it has.",
            "answers": [
                "it's",
                "its"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "An enormous frog sat ………………………………. the grass.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "at",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "‘I am hungry.’ ‘……………………………’",
            "description": "We use ‘so + auxiliary + subject’ to add a positive remark to another positive sentence.",
            "answers": [
                "So am I",
                "So do I",
                "I am so"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "‘I don’t like cricket.’ ‘…………………………. do I.’",
            "description": "We use neither to add a negative addition to a negative idea.",
            "answers": [
                "So",
                "Either",
                "Neither"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Seldom ……………………………….. seen such a dangerous animal.",
            "description": "Inversion is used after negative or restrictive words like hardly, seldom, little, rarely etc.",
            "answers": [
                "I have",
                "have I",
                "did I"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "At no time …………………………………. aware of what was happening.",
            "description": "Inversion is used after negative or restrictive words like hardly, seldom, little, rarely etc.",
            "answers": [
                "she was",
                "was she",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Little …………………………………. realize the danger she faced.",
            "description": "Inversion is used after negative or restrictive words like hardly, seldom, little, rarely etc.",
            "answers": [
                "she did",
                "did she",
                "had she"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I was ………………………………. if you could help me.",
            "description": "We do not normally use think before indirect questions.",
            "answers": [
                "wondering",
                "thinking",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She asked ……………………………… I could help.",
            "description": "Both if and whether can be used to introduce indirect questions.",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "whether",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}